piratestorm.fr 2017-09-25

# BIGPOINT GMBH - PRIVACY POLICY - EFFECTIVE DATE: AUGUST 01, 2017

This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal and non-personal information we collect on [www.bigpoint.com](http://www.bigpoint.com/) and related websites that link to this Privacy Policy (the “Site”) and through the registration and use of games developed and/or published by Bigpoint GmbH (the “Games”), how we use such information and to whom and under what circumstances we may disclose it. By using the Site and Games, which are operated by Bigpoint GmbH you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as described in this Privacy Policy. In this policy, “Bigpoint” refers to Bigpoint, GmbH and its Affiliates, which shall mean subsidiaries, parent companies, joint ventures and other corporate entities under common ownership. We may also refer to Bigpoint as “We” or “Us”. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site or Games.

If you access our games from a third party Social Networking Service (“SNS”), you may be required to also read and accept the SNS’s Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.

## 1 COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

### 1.1 INFORMATION OF CHILDREN UNDER 13*

Before a child under 13 can use a Game, Bigpoint requires registration and consent from a parent. During the registration process only the child’s account name, the child’s email address, the parent’s email address and the child’s password are collected and stored. If the child is under 13, the age of the child is not stored.  
The registration information is only used to confirm the registration and to send the parent a message asking for consent and allowing the parent to activate the child’s user account.  
Once the parent consents to the registration and storage of personal information of the child, this personal information is only used to provide the Game and related services and to send information about Bigpoint Games. Children’s information is not disclosed to third parties except for purposes of operating and providing the Game as detailed in Section 4. Bigpoint does not condition a child’s participation in a Game or activity on the child providing more personal information than is reasonably necessary for that activity.  
Parents can access any personal information collected online, correct or modify any such personal information, or direct us to delete or make no further use of your child’s or your personal information. To do so, please send an email with your request to stop_en@customerservice-bigpoint.com or contact us via mail as detailed in Section 9.  
In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age thirteen without parental consent we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you know or have reason to believe that we might have collected any information from or about a child under thirteen without parental consent, please contact us at stop_en@customerservice-bigpoint.com.  
Bigpoint may collect further personal information from the parent as detailed below.  
*Not all Bigpoint Games are suitable for children under the age of 13. Bigpoint restricts access to such games to players that meet the age requirement.

### 1.2 PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM USERS OVER 13

Bigpoint only collects information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”) from you when you: (1) register on the Site; (2) register to use a Game; (3) contact us; (4) order products and services from us; and (5) participate in our surveys or promotional activities. Personal Information may include the following categories of information: Contact Data (such as your name, address, email address, telephone number); Financial Data (such as your account or credit card information); and Demographic Data (such as zip code and age). If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards, or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys, or Tournament entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

### 1.3 NON –PERSONAL INFORMATION

As part of the standard operation of the Site, we may collect certain non-personal information from you, utilizing any legal available means for data collection, including but not limited to your browser type, operating system, IP address and the domain name from which you accessed the Site. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site and other clickstream data. We may combine the non-personal information we collect from you with your personal information. As part of the data collection we may use cookies, Macromedia Flash local data storage, beacons, third party analytics or any other browser based data collection process to collect the non-personal information described above. For example, we may use cookies or Macromedia Flash local data storage to: (1) allow you to use the Site without having to re-enter your user name and password; (2) monitor Site usage; (3) manage the Site; or (4) conduct research to improve our content and services. Third parties that advertise on the Site may also place cookies or utilize other data collection technologies in their advertisements. A cookie is a small file that may be stored on the hard drive of your computer when you access the Site. You are free to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. To learn about your preferences with respect to our use of Macromedia Flash local data storage, please visit www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/help02.html.

### 1.4 Information Received from an SNS

When you use a Game provided through an SNS such as Facebook, where our Games are also referred to as “applications,” you allow Bigpoint to access certain information from your profile for that site. The information you allow Bigpoint to access varies by Game and the individual SNS platform. Additionally the information allowed is affected by the privacy setting that you have established at the SNS. Information on these settings and how to change them based on your privacy preferences may be found at the SNS where you play our Game. By playing a Game through an SNS you are authorizing Bigpoint, in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, to collect, store, and use any and all information that you agreed the SNS may provide Bigpoint through the SNS Application Programming Interface (“API”). The agreement to this Privacy Policy, the Bigpoint Terms of Service, and any transfer of data from the SNS takes place when you “access” or “allow” (or any similar terms) one of our applications through an SNS.

### 1.5 CHAT AND OTHER PUBLIC COMMUNICATION

We enable users to chat and otherwise communicate in Games and on our websites. We take measures so that chat users cannot disclose personal information, including filters and live moderation. We strongly encourage you not to disclose personal information of yourself or others in such chats or other public communication in our Games our on our websites. Be aware that such information can be read, collected, stored and used by other users. Any such disclosure is at your own discretion and we are not responsible for any information you choose to disclose in such way.

## 2 ACCESS TO INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US

You may access any personal information you provide to us, correct or modify any such personal information, or direct us to make no further use of your personal information. To do so, please send an email with your request to stop_en@customerservice-bigpoint.com.

## 3 USE OF INFORMATION

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to fulfill your requests for products and services; (2) to contact you when necessary; (3) to review Site usage and operations; (4) to address problems with the Site, our business or our products and services; and (5) to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business. We may also use the information we collect from and about you to contact you with information and promotional materials and offers from our company, as well as from our subsidiaries, affiliates, marketing partners, advertisers and other third parties. We do not share personal information of children under 13 with third parties for their marketing purposes. If you would prefer not to receive such promotional communications, please follow the unsubscribe instructions within the email you received when setting up your account.  
In addition to Personal Information and Non-Personal Information collected, you may choose to share information about yourself through other content (“Content”), such as in Games or forums. Any information shared with other players are considered public and at your own discretion.

## 4 DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

Bigpoint GmbH may disclose information collected from and about you as follows: (1) to our related companies, business partners and service providers to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us or to fulfill your product or service request; (2) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the Site Terms of Use, or our rights, or the rights of any third party; (3) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and (4) in the event that our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets. We do not share personal information of children under 13 in this way. You may request that we do not share your personal information with third parties, which may prohibit access to certain features and elements of the Site. To do so, please send an email, with “Disclosure Opt-Out” in the subject line, to stop_en@customerservice-bigpoint.com. We may provide your information to third party companies to perform services on our behalf, including payment processing, data analysis, email deliver, customer support, and various marketing activities. Any third party service provider is required to maintain the confidentiality of the information disclosed to them and to maintain at least the same level of privacy protection as provided by us. Notwithstanding anything else herein, we may partner with third party advertisers who may (themselves or through their partners) place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. These cookies enable more customized ads, content or services to be provided to you. To trigger these cookies, we may pass an encrypted or “hashed” (non-human readable) identifier corresponding to your email address to a Web advertising partner, who may place a cookie on your computer. No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to, these cookies. To opt-out of these cookies, please limit the type of cookies you allow via your web browser settings. You expressly acknowledge that Bigpoint has no liability regarding any data collection process engaged by a third party while you are utilizing a Bigpoint service or while on a Bigpoint website. If you play a Game at a third-party SNS, Bigpoint will be able to access and store information about you as described herein. The categories of information you share will depend, in part, on the privacy settings you have established at the SNS where you access the application. The SNS may allow you to control how you share information with a third-party application (for example, a Bigpoint game as an application on the SNS website) through your privacy settings on the SNS. Bigpoint does not control the privacy settings made available through the SNS to the users of the SNS. Bigpoint refers you to the SNS’ privacy policy posted on the SNS’ site to determine what options are available regarding privacy settings on the SNS.

## 5 HOW TO ACCESS AND MODIFY YOUR INFORMATION

### 5.1 INFORMATION RECEIVED FROM AN SNS WHERE YOU PLAY OUR GAMES

To manage the information Bigpoint receives about you from the SNS where you play the Game, you will need to follow the instructions at that SNS for updating and changing you account privacy settings. Once Bigpoint receives your information from an SNS, that information is stored and used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### 5.2 OTHER METHODS FOR THE MANAGEMENT OF YOUR INFORMATION

  * If you wish to have your information deleted and account deactivated, you may send an e-mail to stop_en@customerservice-bigpoint.com with “Account Information Deactivation” in the subject line. In the e-mail include your account name / UserID in the body of the e-mail. Please note that the deactivation will not affect the storage or retention of any information that is needed for legal or accounting purposes or cannot be removed in the ordinary technological maintenance of an account. Any content you have posted or sent in a Game or on a Bigpoint forum or other similar Bigpoint service may not be able to be deleted.

  * Your California Privacy Rights  
If you are a resident of California, you may request that we not share your personal information with third parties for their own marketing purposes. To do so, please send an email, with “California Opt-Out” in the subject line, to stop_en@customerservice-bigpoint.com.

  * If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@bigpoint.net.

## 6 SECURITY

We have taken certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect and store from Site visitors such as keeping the sensitive data behind a firewall, regular monitoring of our security program and computer systems for evidence of unauthorized use or access to personal information as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store the information.

## 7 THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

The Site may contain links to third-party websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the activities and practices that take place on these sites. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy posted on any site that you may access through the Site.

## 8 CHANGE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate online notice to you.

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, contact us at privacy@bigpoint.net or write us:  
Bigpoint GmbH  
Attention Privacy  
Drehbahn 47-48  
20354 Hamburg  
Germany

Please remember to provide your User-ID, e-mail address and, if necessary, the relevant Game name(s).

If you have reported data privacy concerns and do not feel they have been adequately addressed, you may contact legal@bigpoint.net.
